gas-south.com 2017-07-06

# Gas South | Privacy Policy

**Privacy Policy Purpose:**  
The purpose of this document is to describe how Gas South treats customers’ personal information. The Gas South Privacy Policy as stated in the Terms and Conditions of Service is the following: 

**Privacy Policy:  **  
During the operation of Gas South's business, we collect and use information about our customers, your gas usage and that of other customers, and other relevant information. Gas South obtains and uses information about customers from third parties, including, but not limited to credit reporting agencies, to better enable its business operation. Gas South may disclose such information to its affiliates, or contractors operating on the behalf of Gas South for the purposes of (1) developing or offering new or enhanced products and services or (2) administering and/or collecting on customer accounts. Gas South may disclose such information to parties in connection with proposed business transactions, to credit agencies, or to duly authorized agencies investigating potential hazardous or illegal activity. By providing Gas South with a contact phone number, you expressly agree that Gas South may call or text you at that number with important service notifications related to your account, including collections. These calls or text messages may be made using an automatic dialing system or pre-recorded voice message. You may opt out of receiving autodialed or pre-recorded calls or text messages on your cellular telephone by notifying Gas South by email at optout@gas-south.com or in writing at Gas South LLC, PO Box 723728, Atlanta, GA 31139 with the subject “Gas South: Cell Phone Opt-Out”. Even if you opt out, we may still continue to communicate with you by other means. Your opt-out will not apply to notices of disconnection and other communication that may impact your health and safety or the health and safety of others. By enrolling to purchase natural gas from Gas South, you agree that you will maintain up-to-date contact information with Gas South, including your current home and cell phone number, and that you will notify Gas South immediately of any changes to your phone number(s), email address, or billing address. 

**What information does Gas South gather and how do we use it?** **  
** We collect information about your visits, such as service provider, browser type, operating system, pages accessed on our Web site and the date and time of access to optimize your user experience and enhance your time spent with us online. We also receive information telling us what site you came from. 

When you provide us an e-mail using the Contact Us page, product or promotion enrollment form, we may retain the content of the e-mail, your e-mail address, and our response in order to handle any follow-up questions you may have. We also use this information to measure how effectively we address your concerns. 

We retain your information name, and possibly other personal information, such as mailing address, e-mail address or Gas South account number when appropriate. 

**Who do you share my personal information with?** **  
** We do not sell your name or other private profile information to third parties, and do not intend to do so in the future. We may routinely share your information with our partners and other affiliates. From time to time, we may engage third parties to process information on our behalf; however, Gas South requires that these third parties comply with Gas South’s privacy policies when processing this information. The information Gas South provides to third party vendors will be used solely as defined in each specific vendor’s contract and will not be disseminated to outside parties unless agreed to in writing by both Gas South and the respective third party, or such third party provides consent via Gas South’s website indicating his or her interest in receiving product or services information from related and/or unrelated third party. 

We may also receive information about you from the third-party providers. We may share anonymous, aggregated information about all our users with third parties. 

**How does gas-south.com use cookies and similar technologies?**  
Gas South uses cookies, tags, and other similar technologies to improve your experience on our site. These technologies allow us to recognize your preference information, keep track of your enrollment (if applicable), and facilitate effective site administration. We use the information we collect to enhance your visit to gas-south.com and provide you with information tailored to your needs. You may elect to refuse cookies. Please refer to your browser Help instructions to learn more about cookies. Gas South has engaged third parties acting on Gas South’s behalf, such as DoubleClick, to track and analyze your usage of our site. If you wish, you may [opt out of DoubleClick tracking](http://www.doubleclick.com/us/about_doubleclick/privacy/opting_out.asp).
